[Music]
[音乐]
thank you very much I'm going to skip
非常感谢你，我要跳过
the intro because that was an excellent
介绍，因为那是一个很好的
introduction what is it that we're going
简介我们要去的是什么
to talk about today I decided for this
说说今天，我决定为此
year to add spring io to do a boot loot
年添加spring io做战利品
presentation inspired by loot boxes that
演示受到战利品盒的启发
you may be familiar with inter inter
您可能熟悉国际间
gaming or like me if you have kids that
游戏或喜欢我，如果您有孩子
are into gaming the idea with low loot
以低战利品进入游戏的想法
box if you buy it you don't know exactly
盒子，如果你买，你不知道确切
what's gonna be in it but most of it
里面会有什么，但是大部分
should be good and that's exactly what I
应该很好，这正是我
intend with this presentation so I'm
打算参加这次演讲，所以我
gonna cover various topics related to
将涉及与
using spring boots effectively and
有效地使用春季靴子和
efficiently and I'm sure there will be
高效，我敢肯定会有
something in there for all of you the
在那里为你们所有人
stuff that I'm going to cover is
我要讲的是
actually based on production experience
实际上基于生产经验
which means I'm not just going to show
这意味着我不只是要展示
you things I made up I'm actually going
你我整理的东西我实际上要去
to show you things I made up and then
给你看我做的事，然后
put into production successfully so it
成功投产，所以
should be working for you as well the
应该也为您工作
first thing that we're going to cover is
我们要介绍的第一件事是
the default error page or that evil
默认错误页面或那个邪恶
error rendering that spring boot
春季启动时出现错误
provides for web applications that you
为您提供的Web应用程序
may or may not be familiar with but the
可能会或可能不会熟悉，但是
idea is that if you don't specify
想法是，如果您不指定
anything yourself there is an uncaught
任何你自己的东西都没有
exception happening in a in a spring web
Spring Web中发生的异常
application then if it's a browser
应用程序，如果它是浏览器
client you're going to get a default
客户端，您将获得默认
error page called the white label error
错误页面称为白标错误
page which will just show some details
该页面将仅显示一些详细信息
about the error by default without the
默认情况下不显示错误
stack trace if you're gonna use another
堆栈跟踪，如果您要使用另一个
client programmatic client that will be
客户端程序化客户端
a Jason rendered message showing you the
Jason呈现的消息向您显示
actual error a message in some other
实际错误消息在其他
information we're gonna have a quick
信息，我们将很快
look at that to see what the results of
看那个看看结果如何
that errors are when you are going to
错误是当你要
use validation in your your objects so
在您的对象中使用验证，以便
I'm going to switch to IntelliJ here
我要在这里切换到IntelliJ
just so you know all of the code that I
只是为了让您知道我所有的代码
will be demoing is in a git repo I'll
将在git repo中进行演示，我将
give you the URL at the end so you don't
最后给您URL，这样您就不会
have to take pictures or notes unless
必须拍照或记录笔记，除非
you really like to what you see here is
你真的很喜欢你在这里看到的是
this big enough yes you work we have a
足够大，是的，我们有一个
purchase request here because we're
在这里购买请求，因为我们
going to buy a loop box and the disc ace
要买一个回路盒和光盘王牌
we need to provide two fields we need to
我们需要提供两个领域
provide the actual key or the
提供实际的密钥或
the products that we're gonna purchase
我们要购买的产品
and we're gonna say how much money are
我们要说多少钱
we actually willing to spend on this
我们实际上愿意为此花费
thing now ideally all of these the game
现在理想的是所有这些游戏
vendors would like you to spend as much
供应商希望您花费尽可能多的钱
money as possible but at least in the
尽可能赚钱，但至少在
Netherlands they are getting some
荷兰，他们得到一些
regulations into place on this thing
关于这件事的法规到位
because we're dealing with kids and
因为我们正在和孩子们打交道，
actually some of the bull of the loot is
实际上有些战利品是
actual gambling because you can sell the
实际赌博，因为您可以出售
results so in this case we're limited to
结果，因此在这种情况下，我们仅限于
25 euros that we can actually spend on
我们可以实际花费的25欧元
this with this class what we're gonna do
这堂课我们要做什么
is we're gonna have a super simple
是我们会拥有一个超级简单的
spring boot application over here that
Spring Boot应用程序在这里
simply consists of a single rest
只包含一个休息
controller which takes an incoming post
接收进来的帖子的控制器
request with some JSON and marshals it
请求一些JSON并将其封送
into this loot box purchase request and
放入这个战利品购买请求中，
then simply returns a string that says
然后简单地返回一个字符串，说
hey this worked the important thing here
嘿，这在这里很重要
is the ad valid annotation that you see
是您看到的广告有效注释
on the on the loot box purchase request
在战利品盒购买请求上
that means that before actually calling
这意味着在实际致电之前
your controller method spring will first
您的控制器方法弹簧将首先
perform the actual bean validation
执行实际的bean验证
checks in place on this object and going
在该对象上检查到位并继续
back to the purchase request again both
再次回到购买请求
of these fields are required or not null
这些字段中的必填项或不为null
we have arranged for the money and we
我们已经安排好了钱，我们
have a regular expression pattern saying
有一个正则表达式模式说
that the en should consist of eight
en应该由八个组成
digits so with that let's start the
数字，让我们开始
application and then I'll show you what
应用程序，然后我会告诉你
happens if we pass in first of all a
如果我们首先通过一个
correct request just to prove that
正确的要求只是为了证明
actually works and then make some make
实际工作，然后使一些
some errors in there so applications
那里有些错误，所以应用程序
starting up or actually I have something
开始或实际上我有东西
running on 8080 already let me kill that
在8080上运行已经让我杀了那个
first and then start it up again there
首先，然后在那里再次启动
we go i weld that starting up I'm going
我们去焊接，我开始
to go to a command line here because I'm
去这里的命令行，因为我
going to use HTTP which is like a human
将使用类似于人类的HTTP
friendly curl to make some requests here
友好的卷曲在这里提出一些要求
I'm going to make a post to localhost
我要在本地发布一个帖子
8080 and I need to provide two things I
8080，我需要提供两件事
need to provide a product en which is a
需要提供一个
digits and I need to provide it was a
数字，我需要提供的是
amount of euros but I forgot the field
欧元，但我忘了
name euros to spend is that so euros to
命名欧元要花费的是
spend let's spend 10 euros and we should
花，让我们花10欧元，我们应该
be getting back a response now saying
现在正在回复
this word
这个词
request was valid that's exactly what
要求是正确的
we're after
我们追求
studies work now I want to show you what
现在学习工作，我想告诉你什么
happens if I introduce some errors so
如果我引入一些错误会发生，所以
let's say I say well actually I'm just a
假设我说的很好，实际上我只是一个
poor developer I have no money to spend
可怜的开发商，我没有钱可花
I'm gonna get an error and obviously the
我会得到一个错误，显然
idea is that we need a positive amount
想法是我们需要一个正数
of money but if you look at what we're
钱，但如果你看看我们
seeing on the screen here is that we're
在屏幕上看到的是，我们正在
getting a whole slew of data thrown at
得到大量数据
us receiving some arguments here which
我们在这里收到一些争论
has an asset arguments field not very
有一个资产参数字段不是很
obvious what that is then inside of the
显然那是什么
the outer arguments we have code and we
外部参数有代码，我们
have codes but then there is another
有代码，但还有另一个
field called codes which is actually a
称为代码的字段，实际上是
combination of different properties that
不同属性的组合
spring will try to resolve into an error
春天将尝试解决一个错误
message if it would actually do some
消息，如果它实际上会做一些
resultant here which it doesn't so you
结果这里不是，所以你
get this whole this whole big thing
得到整个这件大事
where a client now needs to make sense
客户现在需要理解的地方
out of this to say oh apparently the
从这个说出来哦，显然
amount of money that passed in was wrong
传入的金额错误
you get similar errors when you leave a
当你离开一个
field out so in this case again you see
外出，所以在这种情况下，您再次看到
that I have this whole bunch of fields
我有一整堆领域
and some error message that says must
和一些错误消息说必须
not be known and then I have to actually
不知道，然后我必须
look really closely to see that it was
仔细观察，发现
the euros to spend in this case that
在这种情况下要花费的欧元
shouldn't have been known and obviously
不应该知道的，显然
we're getting something similar if I
如果我得到类似的东西
create a wrong product en here now I
我现在在这里创建错误的产品
actually have two errors you can see
实际上有两个错误，您可以看到
that there is an error count of two but
有两个错误计数，但是
it doesn't even fit on the screen so I
它甚至不适合屏幕，所以我
have to scroll back up to see that
必须向上滚动才能看到
apparently my product lien must match a
显然我的产品留置权必须与
certain regular expression which it
某些正则表达式
doesn't so this is what you get out of
并非如此，这就是你从中得到的
the box and what's happening here is
盒子，这里发生的是
that when you get this validation error
当您收到此验证错误时
that is causing something in spring
导致春天的事
which is called a field error and if you
这称为字段错误，如果您
would look at the actual field error
会看实际的场错误
class you will see it extends a class
类，您将看到它扩展了一个类
called a default message source
称为默认消息源
resolvable now what that means is that
现在可以解决的意思是
there is stuff in there that could be
里面可能有东西
resolved by using a message source into
通过使用消息源解析为
an actual human readable message but
实际的人类可读消息，但是
what happens is that instead of that
发生的是那个
resultant actually happening these
结果实际发生这些
objects these field errors are simply
对象，这些字段错误只是
marshaled out as is so a lot of the
封送了很多
fields that you saw there with all of
您在那里看到的所有字段
the arguments and the errors in the code
代码中的参数和错误
that's actually coming out of the
那实际上是从
default message whores resolvable and
可以解析的默认消息whores和
some of the subtypes there and I don't
那里有一些亚型，我没有
know about you but this makes my eyes
了解你，但这让我的眼睛
bleed if I see this we try to create in
如果我看到这个，我们尝试在其中创建
the project that I'm currently on we try
我目前正在进行的项目我们尝试
to create actual JSON based API s-- for
创建实际的基于JSON的API-
remote clients right not just for a web
远程客户端不仅适用于Web
browser interpreting this from a reactor
浏览器从反应堆中解释这一点
or an angular app and this is a terrible
或有角度的应用程序，这是一个可怕的
user experience basically to provide to
用户体验基本提供给
your clients so this is something I
您的客户，这就是我
wanted to fix when I when I saw this so
当我看到这个时想修复
wouldn't it be nice if these field
如果这些领域不是很好
errors are in fact instances of
错误实际上是
something that says I can be resolved by
可以说我可以解决的问题
a message source if it was actually
一个消息源，如果它实际上是
resolved into a nice error message and
解决成一个不错的错误消息，
the good news is it's actually quite
好消息是实际上
easy to do that because with spring
容易做到，因为有了春天
boots you can override the default
引导您可以覆盖默认值
implementation of their error attributes
错误属性的实现
which is called the default error
这称为默认错误
attributes and provide your own
属性并提供您自己的
implementation simply by registering a
只需注册一个
bean so that's exactly what I want to
豆，那正是我想要的
show you first so here in my little loot
首先给你看，所以在这里我的小宝贝
package I have a implementation which is
包我有一个实现是
called the resolved error attributes
称为已解决的错误属性
which extends the boots provided default
这扩展了默认提供的靴子
error attributes it isn't used yet
尚未使用的错误属性
because I haven't that component
因为我没有那个成分
annotation here but it's commented out
注释在这里，但已被注释掉
so I'm gonna make that active now and
所以我现在要让它活跃起来
that will automatically ensure that
这将自动确保
spring boots will just pick up this
春季靴子只会拿起这个
class while doing its component scanning
类，同时进行组件扫描
and turns it into a bean what is it that
把它变成豆子那是什么
we're doing here we're injecting a
我们在这里做，我们正在注入
message source and spring boots in a web
网络中的消息源和Spring Boot
app actually provides a default message
应用实际上提供了默认消息
source so I can just rely on that one
源，所以我可以依靠那一个
and then we override this method called
然后我们覆盖这个称为
get error attributes by first calling
通过首先调用获取错误属性
the original method that were overriding
覆盖的原始方法
then extracting a parameter called
然后提取一个名为
errors which will return a list of
错误，将返回列表
object error as you can see over here
您可以在此处看到的对象错误
and then what we do is we say if there
然后我们要做的是说
are any errors in here what we're going
我们要去的地方有什么错误吗
to do is we're just going to loop over
我们要做的就是循环
them and for each one we're gonna do the
他们，我们每个人都要
actual resolving against the message
实际解决消息
source so that's what you see here we do
源，这就是您在这里看到的内容
a message source get message in this
消息源在此获取消息
case I'm just gonna use a US locale
情况下，我只是要使用美国语言环境
because I like English error messages in
因为我喜欢英文错误消息
a Navy I based application and I don't
我基于海军的应用程序，但我没有
care about the actual language that the
关心实际的语言
client may may request for and now we're
客户可能会要求，现在我们
doing one extra thing
多做一件事
because these errors could be regular
因为这些错误可能是正常的
object errors for example if you have a
对象错误，例如，如果您有
validation that spends the the entire
验证花费了整个时间
object or they could be specific to a
对象，或者它们可能特定于
field and if they are specific to a
字段，以及它们是否特定于
field then I don't just want to show
字段，那么我不只是想展示
message that says something like must
消息说像必须
not be know right it doesn't provide you
不知道是对的，它不提供您
with context so we need some additional
与上下文有关，因此我们需要一些其他
context there so in that case we can
在这种情况下，我们可以
downcast and we can say we're going to
沮丧，我们可以说我们要
get the name of the field we want to get
获取我们想要获取的字段的名称
that error message and we also want to
该错误消息，我们也想
have the actual value that people
具有人们的实际价值
provide it so we can say this is the
提供它，所以我们可以说这是
value that didn't match our expectations
不符合我们期望的价值
otherwise we're just going to use the
否则我们将只使用
resolved messages and then we simply
解决的消息，然后我们简单地
override that map with errors with our
使用我们的错误覆盖该地图
result error messages and that's all
结果错误消息，仅此而已
there is to it so with this in place
到此为止
what we can now do is we can restart the
现在我们可以做的是重新启动
application let's see over here and now
应用程序，让我们现在就来看一下
go back to our console here and make a
回到这里的控制台，并进行
new request remember there were two
新要求记得有两个
errors in this request right I have an
这个请求中的错误，我有一个
amount of money which is zero which it
零的钱
shouldn't be and I have an extra number
不应该，我有一个额外的号码
in my product en and what I'm seeing now
在我的产品中以及我现在所看到的
is that zoom in a bit is that I'm just
是放大一点就是我只是
gonna get an error array here with two
会有两个错误数组
human readable errors saying the product
易读错误说明产品
en must match these eight digits and the
en必须与这八位数字匹配，并且
euro suspend must be greater than zero
欧元暂停交易必须大于零
but the actual value provided was zero
但提供的实际值为零
so that's really all it takes to to get
所以这实际上就是获得
a bit more saying defaults basically for
多说一些基本的默认值
rendering these error messages and what
呈现这些错误消息以及什么
I like about this approach is it
我喜欢这种方法是
prevents you from having to do custom
避免您必须进行自定义
error handling everywhere and you can
错误处理无处不在，您可以
actually go with most of the stuff that
实际上与大多数
spring boot provides for you but take
弹簧靴为您提供，但要
away some of the Crofts that you get
离开一些你得到的小农场
when simply marshalling out these these
当简单地整理这些
field errors as is so that's the first
现场错误，所以这是第一个
demo that I wanted to show you and with
我想向您展示的演示
that we're gonna have a look at another
我们要去看看另一个
feature I would actually be tricky just
我实际上会很棘手
before lunch there was a really good
午餐之前，真的很棒
presentation here from from Brian and
来自Brian和的演讲
this bring buti'm about building web
这带来了关于建立网络
applications and they actually showed us
应用程序，它们实际上向我们展示了
some of these sports what I'm going to
其中一些运动是我要去的
show you a bit extra so even if you were
给你多展示一点，即使你是
there don't worry you will learn
不用担心，您会学到
something new spring boot has a feature
新的春季靴子有一些功能
which allows you to bind configuration
允许您绑定配置
properties basically just can
属性基本上可以
configuration coming out of some
一些配置
property sores in the environments to an
环境中的财产疮
instance of javabean and then you can
javabean的实例，然后就可以
just inject that being into your code
只是将其注入您的代码中
and you can read the actual
您可以阅读实际的
configuration just by calling some
通过调用一些配置
gather methods this is nice to use
收集方法，这很好用
especially if you have a lot of related
特别是如果您有很多相关
configuration you can just group them up
配置，您可以将它们分组
as a set of properties belonging to a
作为属于一个的一组属性
single class and then have some common
单班，然后有一些共同点
naming prefix in your properties to make
在属性中命名前缀
sure that everything that started with
确保一切始于
that gets bound to that class that's
绑定到那个类
actually a whole bunch of words to
实际上是一堆单词
explain this but it's actually much
解释一下，但实际上很多
easier to just show you so let's look at
更容易向您展示，让我们来看一下
an example for this we have let's close
一个例子，让我们结束
all of this first we have another
首先，我们有另一个
project here which provides a class
这里提供一个类的项目
called loots properties you can see the
所谓的抢劫属性，您可以看到
theme here in this case we say we want
在这种情况下，我们说我们想要
to have a configuration properties class
具有配置属性类
and all of the properties that we use to
以及我们用于的所有属性
configure this thing will be prefixed
配置这个东西会前缀
with loots and then we have two
与抢劫，然后我们有两个
properties we have an allow transfer
我们有允许转让的属性
boolean which tells me that if I buy
布尔值告诉我，如果我购买
some lewd am I allowed to transfer it to
我允许一些淫荡转移到
some other player in the game for money
游戏中其他一些玩家为了钱
like this is the thing that's actually
像这样的东西实际上
illegal now in the Netherlands for for
现在在荷兰非法
underage people because it's gambling
未成年人，因为它在赌博
and we have an enum that specifies the
我们有一个枚举指定
game for which we want to buy some loot
我们要为其购买战利品的游戏
I've actually inline that so we have
我实际上已经内联了，所以我们有
overwatch fortnight and FIFA here
守望先锋两周和国际足联在这里
because according to Wikipedia those are
因为根据维基百科，这些是
games you can buy loot for I'm not
您可以购买战利品的游戏，因为我不是
personally a gamer now with this thing
现在是这个游戏的个人玩家
in place what we can do is we have a
我们可以做的就是
little spring boot application class
小弹簧启动应用程序类
here and first a thing you may notice
首先，您可能会注意到
here is that we have an enable
这是我们有一个启用
configuration properties annotation
配置属性注释
there's actually two ways to enable
实际上有两种方法可以启用
support for a configuration properties
支持配置属性
annotated class either you simply turn
带注释的类，您只需打开
that class into a spring bean by
该类由
annotating it with that component for
用该组件对其进行注释
example making it eligible for component
示例使其符合组件条件
scanning or you explicitly mention it as
扫描或您明确提及为
saying this is a configuration
说这是一个配置
properties class that I would like to
我想要的属性类
use and be instantiated using the enable
使用并使用enable实例化
configuration properties after that an
之后的配置属性
instance of that properties object is
该属性对象的实例是
simply Auto wired into the class here
只需在这里自动连线到班级
into the code and then when it's
进入代码，然后在
injected we're going to print
注入我们将要打印
the game and the transfer that have been
游戏和转移已经
configured so I haven't configured
配置好了，所以我还没有配置
anything yet let me double check that I
还有什么让我仔细检查一下
didn't know I haven't configured
不知道我还没有配置
anything yet so first off what I'm gonna
任何事情，所以首先我要
do is I'm going to just start the
我要做的只是开始
application here and what we should be
应用在这里，我们应该是
seeing is that no configuration was
看到没有配置
actually provided so both of these
实际上提供了这两个
properties should just be null so I'm
属性应该只是空，所以我
starting up my application and indeed we
启动我的应用程序，实际上我们
can see here that we do get an instance
可以在这里看到我们确实有一个实例
of Duluth properties but the game and
的德卢斯属性，但游戏和
the transfer a lot or both no so that's
转移很多，或者两者都没有，所以
what we expect what we can do now is any
我们期望我们现在能做什么
way that Springwood provides us with we
Springwood为我们提供的方式
can define some configuration properties
可以定义一些配置属性
for this so an obvious way is through
为此，一个明显的方法是通过
the application properties here which is
这里的应用程序属性是
currently empty so what I could do is I
目前是空的，所以我能做的是
can say prefix with loot because that's
可以说出带有战利品的前缀，因为那是
the prefix that we configured and then
我们配置的前缀，然后
say what do we have we have game so
说我们有什么我们有游戏所以
let's say I want to buy for FIFA and the
假设我想购买FIFA，
other one was allow transfer now we're
另一个是允许转移，现在我们
going to set that to true and then we're
将其设置为true，然后我们
going to see if these words as expected
看看这些话是否如预期
so restart the application and that we
所以重新启动应用程序，然后我们
see now that our string which we
现在看到我们的字符串
actually specified in lowercase FIFA is
小写FIFA中实际指定的是
actually matched on to the write in
实际匹配写入
'value so that binding happens
值以使绑定发生
automatically and indeed our boolean has
自动，实际上我们的布尔值具有
been configured as well and now we've
也已经配置好了，现在我们已经
set that to true so this is basically
设置为true，所以这基本上是
what was also shown in the previous
上一个也显示了什么
presentation so what is what it shows
演示文稿，那么它显示了什么
you is this is a nice easy way to group
你是这是一个很好的分组方法
a number of related configuration
一些相关的配置
properties and it's easy to access this
属性，很容易访问
you don't need to use a lot of Ed value
您不需要使用很多Ed值
annotations you can just inject this
您可以注入注解
Java object so it's nice but it's not
Java对象，所以很好，但不是
that different from actually just using
与实际使用不同
add value we can also easily use things
增加价值，我们也可以轻松地使用事物
like default values with with that value
如带有该值的默认值
as well as with configuration properties
以及配置属性
so you may wonder like what do I really
所以你可能想知道我到底是什么
gain in doing this there's actually two
这样做的好处实际上有两个
important features that I quickly want
我很快想要的重要功能
to show you first of all you can get IDE
首先向您展示您可以获得IDE
support for this and you're probably
支持这个，你可能
familiar with that already if you're
如果您已经熟悉了
using spring boots because you get code
使用弹簧靴，因为您会得到代码
assist in your Java EE
协助您的Java EE
if you're editing things like
如果您正在编辑诸如
application properties but you can get
应用程序属性，但您可以获得
that for your own things as well
也是为了你自己的事情
the other thing I quickly want to show
我很快想展示的另一件事
you is support for bean validation
您支持Bean验证
similar to the bean validation that we
类似于我们的bean验证
had in spring MVC so let's have a quick
春季有MVC，所以让我们快速
look at that first of all we're going to
看看首先我们要
make sure that if I am in here I want to
确保如果我在这里我想
be able to simply say something like
能够简单地说出类似
this do control space and then get some
这样可以控制空间，然后得到一些
suggestions currently I'm not getting
目前我没有得到建议
anything but I can tell spring to at
除了我能告诉春天到
compile time do some processing for me
编译时为我做一些处理
and based on my configuration properties
并根据我的配置属性
annotated classes generate a file that
带注释的类生成一个文件，该文件
will be understood by all major Java IDE
所有主要的Java IDE都可以理解
slike IntelliJ and Eclipse so for that
像IntelliJ和Eclipse一样
the only thing you need to do basically
您基本上唯一需要做的就是
is to enable support for this
是为了为此提供支持
configuration processor
配置处理器
I've also configured my IntelliJ to
我还将IntelliJ配置为
actually have support for annotation
实际上支持注释
processing tools so this should be
处理工具，所以应该
enough actually if you don't can enable
如果您不能启用，那么实际上足够
that explicitly you should actually do a
明确地，你实际上应该做一个
maven build now in the command line to
maven现在在命令行中构建到
have this affected the result of this is
有这个影响的结果是
that actually it looks like it didn't do
实际上看起来好像没有做
so I need to trigger a build there we go
所以我需要触发一个构建
the result of this will be that there
其结果将是
will be a new file generated for me that
将是为我生成的一个新文件
tells the IDE exactly what what new
告诉IDE到底有什么新内容
types are there let's see if it works
有类型，让我们看看它是否有效
because I don't see it yes maybe I do
因为我看不到，也许我会
need to have a command line there we go
我们需要有一个命令行
nope so um what you see here is now when
不，所以你现在在这里看到的是
I do control space I actually get a
我控制空间我实际上得到了
little I'll transfer which is a boolean
小我会转移这是一个布尔值
and a game also note that the allowed
游戏也请注意，
transfer actually is using a dash here
转移实际上是在这里使用破折号
this is called cabal case you know I'll
这叫做阴谋案，你知道我会
get back to that so this is nice right I
回到那个，所以这很好，我
can do this and now because the IDE
可以做到这一点，因为IDE
understands is the boolean I get code
理解是我得到代码的布尔值
assist on those values as well
协助这些价值观
same thing is true for the game so I
游戏也是如此，所以我
could configure that and I can choose
可以配置，我可以选择
that right I just need to press ENTER
那个权利，我只需要按Enter
all the time until my application works
一直到我的应用程序正常工作
that's the ideal workflow for every
这是每个人的理想工作流程
developer on the other hand it doesn't
另一方面，开发人员不会
actually tell me exactly what these
真的告诉我这些是什么
values do and ideally as a developer I
价值观，而且理想情况下，作为开发人员我
would like to have an idea of what what
想知道什么
do these things actually mean so what I
这些事情实际上意味着什么，我
can do here is I can go into my
可以在这里做的是我可以进入我的
configuration object and I can do some
配置对象，我可以做一些
Java doc
Java文档
going to do that directly on the field
将直接在现场进行
so that's actually what you're supposed
所以这实际上就是你应该的
to be doing here so I can say defines if
要在这里做，所以我可以说定义
transfer is allowed and there's a typo
允许转移，有错别字
there but that's okay and then the other
在那里，但是没关系，然后另一个
thing I can do is say what game are we
我能做的就是说我们在玩什么
buying loot for like that so what will
那样买战利品
happen now is this information will be
现在发生的是此信息将
taken into account by this annotation
该注释考虑在内
processor tool we put in the same meta
我们将处理器工具放在同一个meta中
data file read by the ID and now if I go
数据文件通过ID读取，如果我去了
back here I can actually see that for
回到这里，我实际上可以看到
example if I start to configured this
如果我开始配置此示例
there we go let's do it like that I can
我们去吧，那样做，我可以
actually see the documentation here that
实际上在这里看到文档
says what game are we buying loot for
说我们要买什么游戏来抢劫
right but this is perfect because this
是的，但这很完美，因为
means that I can actually start to
意味着我实际上可以开始
discover the available configuration as
发现可用的配置为
a developer on the application that I'm
我正在使用的应用程序上的开发人员
working on with my team see what values
与我的团队一起工作，看看有什么价值
are there it will also show you default
在那里也会显示默认值
values if you have configured anything
值，如果您已配置任何内容
like that and you can provide some some
这样，您可以提供一些
built-in documentation as well the other
内置文档以及其他
thing we can do now is we actually go
我们现在能做的就是实际去
back into this thing
回到这个东西
and we can sorry the properties we can
我们可以抱歉的属性
annotate it without validated as soon as
请在未经验证的情况下立即对其进行注释
we do that spring boot will
我们做那个春季靴子
automatically apply some bean validation
自动应用一些bean验证
to instances of this thing after our
在我们之后这个东西的实例
properties have been bound so what that
属性已经绑定，那
means is that we could say well the
意思是我们可以说的很好
allowed transfer here that's actually
实际允许的转移
required to be configured i don't allow
需要配置，我不允许
this thing to be null and i probably
这个东西为空，我可能
want to do the same thing for the game
想要为游戏做同样的事情
here so I'm gonna do that and I'm gonna
在这里，我要去做，我要去
go back into my application properties
回到我的应用程序属性
and I'm just going to specify the
我将要指定
allowed transfer but I'm going to leave
允许转让，但我要走了
out the game so right now what should
所以现在应该退出游戏
happen is if I restart my application
发生的是如果我重新启动我的应用程序
spring boot will instantiate an instance
Spring Boot将实例化一个实例
of my properties object will do the
我的属性对象将做
binding it will then perform the
绑定它将执行
validation and says hey you're actually
验证并说嘿，你实际上是
missing a field there so it's gonna
那里缺少一个领域，所以它将
crash at startup but rather than just
在启动时崩溃，而不仅仅是
showing you some stack trace and then
向您显示一些堆栈跟踪，然后
forcing you to make sense of that it
强迫你理解它
shows a nice error report where it says
显示一个不错的错误报告，上面写着
hey I couldn't actually bind to an
嘿，我实际上无法绑定到
instance of this loot properties thing
战利品属性的实例
the
的
there was a lute game property that you
你有琵琶游戏的财产
were supposed to configure but it was
应该配置，但是
actually no and it shouldn't be no so
实际上不，不应该这样
this also means that it becomes very
这也意味着它变得非常
easy for people to see if the
容易让人看到
application starts up that they forgot
他们忘记了的应用程序启动
to configure some required property
配置一些必需的属性
where it should be where it's expected
应该在预期的地方
etcetera etc so that's a really
etcetera等，这真的是
convenient feature and it's especially
方便的功能，尤其是
nice I think for either big projects
不错，我认为无论是大型项目
where you have lots of people working on
你有很多人在工作
a large code base and not everyone is
大量的代码库，并不是每个人都是
intimately intimately familiar with
亲密地熟悉
every feature so now you can discover
每个功能，因此您现在可以发现
the actual configuration that's
实际的配置是
available for your application rather
适用于您的应用程序
than just having to document it
不仅仅是记录
somewhere and then hope that the
某个地方，然后希望
documentation is actually kept in sync
文档实际上保持同步
with the actual code because this stuff
与实际的代码，因为这东西
is self documenting I am currently using
正在自我记录我当前正在使用的
this a lot in a project where we're
我们在一个项目中有很多
building a set of micro services that
建立一套微服务
have some shared auto-configuration
有一些共享的自动配置
libraries and all of that other
图书馆和所有其他
configuration has some configuration in
配置中有一些配置
there as well to to tune it so by
还有在那里进行调整
providing these sort of configuration
提供这类配置
properties instances with your other
与其他属性实例
configuration again it becomes very easy
再次配置它变得非常容易
for people to discover what it is
让人们发现它是什么
exactly that they can configure and that
正是他们可以配置的
they are supposed to configure when
他们应该配置何时
they're using some of your features
他们正在使用您的某些功能
smarter things are quickly mentioned and
很快就会提到更聪明的事情，
then we move on is that if you're using
那么我们继续说，如果您正在使用
these Springwood actually where your
这些斯普林伍德居然
functionality there's also a dedicated
功能还有一个专用的
endpoints by default is called config
默认情况下，端点称为config
drops on which you can see all of the
可以看到所有的
instantiated configuration properties in
中的实例化配置属性
the application context and their actual
应用程序上下文及其实际
values which will include your own
包含您自己的值
custom configuration properties
定制配置属性
obviously if you specify those and they
显然，如果您指定了这些
announced in the upcoming spring boot to
在即将到来的春季靴子中宣布
the to that if you have an ADD
如果您有ADD
configuration properties class it will
配置属性类
actually be automatically components can
实际上是自动组件可以
so you don't actually even need the add
因此您实际上甚至不需要添加
component already the other annotation
组件已经是其他注释
that I showed you anymore which makes it
我告诉你了，这使得
even easier to start using this
开始使用它更容易
functionality now that was the thing I
现在功能就是我
showed you were actually built in
表明你实际上是内置的
already into the IDE it suggested a name
已经进入IDE，它建议了一个名称
like loot allow transfer which will
像战利品一样允许转移
which was bound to a Java property
绑定到Java属性
called allow transfer with camel casing
叫骆驼套允许转移
what I could also do is I could actually
我也可以做的是
specify I like something like an
指定我喜欢像
environment variable all uppercase with
环境变量全部为大写
underscores that will work in binding as
下划线将与
well now I notice before when someone
好吧，现在我注意到当有人
was
原为
asking about people still using spring
询问人们仍然在使用弹簧
boots one-to-five that some hands went
一只手到五只靴子
up if you wanted this functionality
如果您需要此功能
called relaxed binding in spring boot
在春季靴子中被称为宽松装订
1.5 and below you actually were forced
1.5及以下你实际上是被迫
to use a configuration properties class
使用配置属性类
like this however for those of you
像这样对你们这些人
thinking that that's still the case
认为情况仍然如此
they actually completely overhauled this
他们实际上彻底修改了这个
binding mechanism in spring Mbutu so in
春季Mbutu中的绑定机制
spring boots you as long as you're using
只要您使用，春季靴子
what is called kabob casing lower case
什么叫烤肉肠小写
with dashes you can even use simple add
带破折号，您甚至可以使用简单的添加
value annotations and you will get the
值注释，您将获得
relaxed binding support so you're not
宽松的绑定支持，因此您不会
you're no longer force basically to use
您基本上不再需要使用
a configuration for these object just
这些对象的配置
for that one purpose just so you know I
为此目的，所以你知道我
have no idea by the way why it's called
不知道为什么叫它
kabob casing but with that we're going
烤肉肠衣但是我们要
to move on metrics cardinality this
继续衡量指标基数
product that I was mentioning is
我提到的产品是
actually my first project that we are
实际上是我的第一个项目
heavily using the new metric support
大量使用新的指标支持
from spring boot in and while working
从春季启动和工作时
with that I did some tuning and and so
这样我做了一些调整，等等
and some some other things that I
还有一些其他的事情
quickly wanted to show you here
很快想在这里告诉你
including this thing about
包括这件事
dimensionality so if you haven't seen
维度，所以如果你还没有看到
that yet starting with spring Mbutu they
从春天Mbutu开始，他们
have built-in integration with something
与某些东西有内置的集成
called micrometer which is an
称为千分尺
abstraction layer for for exposing
用于暴露的抽象层
metrics to a variety of time-series
各种时间序列的指标
metrics databases and a lot of
指标数据库和很多
instrumentation out of the box for all
开箱即用的仪器
sorts of spring components so you get
各种弹簧组件，使您得到
metrics about your MVC controllers rest
有关您的MVC控制器的指标
templates JVM itself Tomcat etc etc and
模板JVM本身Tomcat等
that's super useful for seeing what is
这对于了解什么是超级有用的
happening with your application there
您的应用程序在那里发生
were some demos in the previous
是以前的一些演示
presentation here basically what metrics
这里介绍基本上是什么指标
are is it's a some statistic gathered in
这是一些统计数据吗
typically over something like one minute
通常超过一分钟
that exposes a value that could be a
暴露了一个可能是
counter it could be the duration of
相反，可能是持续时间
something it could be just a number of
可能只是一些
something like the price that you had
像你所拥有的价格
for selling a product or something like
用于销售产品或类似的东西
that and there will be some associated
那将有一些相关的
key value pairs with with every with
键值对与每一个
every piece of data there and those
那里的每一个数据
values are called either dimensions or
值称为维度或
tags they're the same thing so for
标签，他们是同一回事
example when you're using a rest
休息时的例子
templates with spring boot app you can
带有Spring Boot应用程序的模板，您可以
automatically get some metrics out of
自动从中获取一些指标
that whenever you make
每当你做
a request that will tell you the
一个可以告诉您的请求
duration of that request how long did it
该请求的持续时间了多长时间
take to handle this but in addition to
采取处理这一点，但除了
that you will see what URL were
您将看到什么URL
recalling what HTTP method we were using
回顾我们使用的HTTP方法
was it Gator post what was the status
是Gator发布的状态是什么
code of the response was it successful
响应代码是否成功
or not and a bunch of other stuff and
还是没有，还有其他一些东西
this gives you a very easy way to get
这给你一个很简单的方法
insight into the workings of your
洞察您的运作方式
application now the idea behind these
现在应用这些背后的想法
tags like the HTTP status for example or
标签，例如HTTP状态或
the speed method that you use is that
您使用的速度方法是
you can use them for things like
您可以将它们用于诸如
filtering in your monitoring tools so
过滤您的监视工具，以便
maybe I want to say only give me the
也许我只想说给我
success requests that I made that
成功要求我提出
resulted in the 200 okay or something in
结果200没问题
the 200 range and I'm not interested in
200范围，我不感兴趣
the 500 or maybe I actually want to see
500，也许我真的很想看看
both what I want to see them separately
我想分别看到它们
so I can compare how many success
所以我可以比较多少成功
requests I'm making to how many requests
我要处理的请求数
are actually failing so that's that's
实际上是失败的，那就是
very useful functionality but it's only
非常有用的功能，但这仅仅是
useful if the actual number of values
如果值的实际数量有用
for one particular tag or one particular
对于一个特定的标签或一个特定的
dimension is somewhat limited if it's
尺寸在某种程度上受到限制
unbounded if it grows too much it will
如果它增长太多，它将无限制
just become too much information it
只是成为太多信息而已
doesn't actually work if you even do
甚至不能实际工作
that because spring boots rightfully so
因为春天正确地引导
refuses to keep all of that information
拒绝保留所有这些信息
in memory and then pass it on to your
在内存中，然后将其传递给您
metrics tool all at the same time so you
指标工具都可以同时使用
need to make sure that you somewhat
需要确保你有点
limit the amount of values that any one
限制任何一个值的数量
tag can actually have so to show you
标签实际上可以向您显示
that let's look at another example that
让我们看另一个例子
I created for you where we have a simple
我为您创建了一个简单的
web application with a controller which
带有控制器的Web应用程序
is here what this controller does is
这是控制器的作用
let's see just a seconds yeah so this
让我们看一秒钟是的，所以这
controller simply has two endpoints one
控制器仅具有两个端点
allows you to perform a search request
允许您执行搜索请求
and that search request takes a request
该搜索请求接受了一个请求
parameter pulled query over here so that
参数将查询拉到此处，以便
means that when we make a request we can
意味着当我们提出请求时，我们可以
pass in some some query string and then
传递一些查询字符串，然后
in a regular application this thing
在常规应用中，这东西
would perform an actual search what I'm
会进行实际的搜索
doing instead is every two out of three
而是三分之二
times I'm just saying okay we tried but
有时我只是说好，我们尝试过
the we ran a search results and after
我们运行了搜索结果，然后
one other three requests I'm just going
我要去的另外三个请求
to throw back a custom status to have
放弃自定义状态
some different values there in the
那里有些不同的值
nemetrix and we have another one where I
nemetrix，我们还有另外一个
can post to slash lose with that I now
现在可以发布大幅削减的消息
have this spring boot application that
有这个春季启动应用程序
implements the command line runner
实现命令行运行程序
interface so what it does is it uses a
界面，所以它使用的是
rest template that I have configured to
我已配置为的其余模板
make a bunch of requests to this MVC
向此MVC发出一堆请求
controller after the application has
应用程序后的控制器
started up so I'm just gonna make a
开始，所以我要做一个
thousand requests or actually I'm gonna
千个请求，或者实际上我要
make two thousand requests because I'm
提出两千个要求，因为我
going to make a thousand requests to
将要发出一千个请求
every controller method for the query 1
查询的每个控制器方法1
here I'm just going to append the actual
在这里，我将附加实际的
number of the requests that we're doing
我们正在执行的请求数
so it's going to be 0 up and until + 9 +
所以它将是0直到+ 9 +
let's start this up and let's then see
让我们开始，然后看看
what happens so while they starts up you
当他们启动你时会发生什么
should know that for this application
应该知道这个应用程序
I've also here in the palm configured an
我也在这里配置了一个
HTTP client actually spring boot will
HTTP客户端实际上是春季启动
automatically pick that up and it will
自动捡起它，它将
use my apache ICP client rather than
使用我的apache ICP客户而不是
just a java.net with your ID to make the
只是一个带有您ID的java.net，
request and i've configured the actuator
请求，我已经配置了执行器
support and that's actually important
支持，这实际上很重要
here because that will activate support
在这里，因为这将激活支持
for metrics so looking at my console I
有关指标，所以看着我的控制台
can see that I made a bunch of requests
可以看到我提出了很多要求
with different results what I can do now
结果不同，我现在可以做什么
is I can actually go to a browser here
我真的可以在这里浏览器吗
go to localhost 8080 slash X waiter it's
转到localhost 8080斜杠X服务员
less metrics and what I will see then is
较少的指标，然后我将看到的是
an overview of all of the different
所有不同的概述
metrics that were exposed by by my
由我公开的指标
application so that's quite a lot one of
应用程序，所以其中很多
them here is a metric which is called
他们在这里是一个指标，称为
HTTP server metrics requests I'm sorry
HTTP服务器指标要求，很抱歉
so what we see here is that we made a
所以我们在这里看到的是，我们做了一个
total of 2002 requests because it's also
总共2002要求，因为它也是
counting these requests that I'm
计算我的这些要求
currently making to my event actuator
目前正在为我的事件执行器
endpoints I can see how long it took to
端点，我可以看到花了多长时间
make those requests I can see some
提出这些要求，我可以看到一些
additional tags or dimensions so we can
其他标签或尺寸，以便我们可以
see we did both posts and get requests
看到我们都发布了帖子并收到了请求
and we made requests to slash search to
并且我们要求将搜索大幅削减至
the metrics my browser a1 to the
我的浏览器a1的指标
I can and to dilute one we had different
我可以并且稀释我们有不同的
outcomes we had a client errors and
结果我们有一个客户错误，
successes because we had four twos 242
成功，因为我们有四个二242
nines and so that's very useful
九分，所以这非常有用
information in this case this is
在这种情况下的信息是
actually rather limited if you would
如果您愿意的话，实际上相当有限
export this to an actual metrics
将此导出为实际指标
database you'll you will be able to get
数据库，您将可以获取
much more out of this but I also have
除此之外，我还有
client requests here and this shows me
客户在这里的要求，这告诉我
information from my rest templates the
我其余模板中的信息
timer of the rest template operation as
其余模板操作的计时器为
it says here now if I were looking at
它说现在如果我在看
the values here then you see that there
这里的值，那么你看到那里
is a bunch of different URLs here
这里有很多不同的URL
because I have different query
因为我有不同的查询
parameters for everything there is one
一切的参数都有一个
for Lutz and then there's a bunch of
为卢兹，然后有一堆
other ones for query but this is not a
其他查询，但这不是一个
thousand this is close to a hundred and
千，这接近一百
then it stops there are no additional
然后它停止了，没有其他
tags here and the reason for that is
标签在这里，其原因是
that it would simply be too much
那简直太过分了
information so if I'm going to scroll
信息，所以如果我要滚动
back here a bit then somewhere close to
回到这里再靠近某处
the top we will see an error message
在顶部，我们将看到一条错误消息
here and this this warning actually says
在这里，这个警告实际上说
hey you reach the maximum number of your
嘿，您达到了最大数量
itex for the ACP client requests are you
ACP客户请求的itex是
using your I variable x' so that's a
使用您的I变量x'，这是一个
good question I'm not it was interesting
好问题，我不是很有趣
I was at a talk today from Martine and
我今天在Martine和
Olga about spring clouds and they were
奥尔加关于春天的云，他们
actually using a UI template builder to
实际上使用UI模板构建器来
construct URLs with query parameters and
使用查询参数构造网址，并
then passing them to the rest templates
然后将它们传递给其余模板
you would get exactly this result so
您将完全得到此结果，因此
you're gonna probably run into this
你可能会遇到这个
error now in this case it would actually
现在在这种情况下会出现错误
be rather straightforward for me to fix
对我来说很简单
this because what I could do is in my
这是因为我能做的就是
demo class here I could just say you
示范课，我可以说你
know what I should be using a
知道我应该使用
placeholder here and now say just pass
占位符在这里，现在说刚刚过去
the place all there as so far our
到目前为止所有的地方
parameter right here and this will
参数在这里，这将
actually fix the problem if you do this
实际解决问题，如果您这样做
in this case I'm not actually going to
在这种情况下，我实际上并不会
demo it because I want to show you some
演示一下，因为我想给你看一些
other stuff as well but this is not
还有其他东西，但这不是
always an option right you may be making
总是您可能会做出的选择权
requests to URLs that were simply passed
对简单传递的URL的请求
in from somewhere else and you may not
从其他地方进来，你可能不会
actually have the option of saying I'm
实际上可以选择说我
just going to rewrite this and do some
只是要重写它并做一些
some URL query parameter so in that case
一些URL查询参数，在这种情况下
what do you do and that's exactly what I
你在做什么，那正是我
wanted to show you so here what
想在这里告诉你什么
I have in my loot package is some
我的战利品包里有一些
configuration for metrics and it's
指标的配置，
disabled right now what I'm going to
现在禁用我要去的东西
enable it and then what you see here is
启用它，然后您在这里看到的是
that we have a beam here of type meter
我们这里有一个米类型的光束
filter which allows you to actually say
过滤器，可以让您实际说出
I'm going to look at metrics before they
我要先看一下指标
are being published and I can do some
正在出版，我可以做一些
post-processing on them so in this case
对它们进行后期处理
what I'm doing is I'm saying if there is
我在说的是如果有
a tag called URI and that could be from
一个名为URI的标签，该标签可能来自
a rest template it could be from
其余模板可能来自
something else but if it's a URI I'm
其他的东西，但如果是URI，我就是
going to check if there is a question
要检查是否有问题
mark signaling the start of some query
标记表示某些查询开始
parameters and if there is I'm just
参数，如果有我只是
gonna call it off otherwise I'm just
要取消它，否则我就是
gonna leave it as is there is another
要离开它，因为还有另一个
thing here that I'm quickly just showing
我很快在这里展示的东西
you because I think it's a nice feature
你，因为我认为这是一个不错的功能
there is also a monitoring request tag
还有一个监控请求标签
and meter filter here we have some
和仪表过滤器在这里，我们有一些
instances in our application of
我们的应用实例
operations that are not really called
未真正调用的操作
that often by clients but we are calling
通常是客户打来的，但我们正在打电话
our own operations a lot for monitoring
我们自己的操作需要大量监控
tools just continuously checking of our
工具只是不断检查我们的
application is up and if it's healthy so
应用程序是否正常，是否健康
sometimes those tests those monitoring
有时那些测试那些监测
tests will actually drain out the actual
测试实际上会耗尽实际
traffic so it becomes hard to see how
交通，因此很难看到
many real requests people are making so
人们提出了许多真正的要求
what I'm doing here is I'm actually
我在这里做的是我实际上
looking for a request attribute from the
从中寻找请求属性
incoming HTTP request that I called X
我叫X的传入HTTP请求
monitoring and if that is there and it's
监视，如果在那里，那是
set to true I'm gonna put a tag in my
设置为true我要在我的标签上放一个标签
metric saying oh this was a monitoring
指标说哦，这是一个监视
request and otherwise I'm gonna set it
请求，否则我要设置它
to false and with that it will become
虚假的，它将成为
very easy again to do filtering in your
再次非常容易地对您进行过滤
actual monitoring tooling to see the
实际的监控工具，以了解
traffic caused by your own monitoring
您自己的监控导致的流量
versus that which is actual clients
与实际客户相比
generated production traffic with this
由此产生的生产流量
in place we can restart the application
我们可以重新启动应用程序
yep stop memory run and what we should
是的，停止内存运行以及我们应该做什么
be seeing now is if I run the same thing
现在看到的是如果我运行相同的东西
again and look at the metrics we see
再来看看我们看到的指标
that there is only one URL or on your
只有一个网址或您的网址上
eye for all of the rest template calls
关注其余所有模板调用
that was made because we're stripping
那是因为我们要剥离
those query parameters so the
这些查询参数
application has run we're gonna refresh
应用程序已运行，我们将刷新
and now indeed we see that there's just
现在确实，我们看到
two values there is slash search and
两个值是斜杠搜索和
there is slash loot right so this is
这里有一个斜线战利品，所以这是
something to keep in mind this is just
要记住的一点是
one example for a rest template but this
休息模板的一个例子，但这
is something in general that you should
一般而言，您应该
think about when you're using metrics if
考虑一下您何时使用指标
you're gonna add custom
您将添加自定义
you should not just have like an
你不应该只喜欢
unbounded number of potential values
无限数量的潜在价值
because that goes against the idea of
因为那违背了
having these dimensional metrics and
具有这些尺寸指标
this is a nice way to actually keep that
这是保持这一点的好方法
within some bounds
在一定范围内
okay billers and customizers is another
好的帐单和定制器是另一个
topic that is actually quite common to
实际上很常见的话题
to spring boot using in the typical
在典型情况下使用弹簧靴
spring app you will use a lot of helper
春天的应用程序，您将使用很多帮助器
classes some of them can be from spring
某些课程可能是春季课程
itself like a rest template but also
本身就像一个休息模板，但也
things like jackson object mappers and
像杰克逊对象映射器和
they typically need some configuration
他们通常需要一些配置
so usually people will just grid and
所以通常人们只会把
directly in the class where they need
直接在他们需要的班级上
them like a field or maybe you have a
他们像田野，或者你有一个
beam that you create for that like oh
你为此创造的光束
you're on a slide where we simply return
您在幻灯片上，我们只是返回
a new rest camp let's the problem is
一个新的休憩营地，我们的问题是
fairly often spring frameworks or things
经常出现Spring框架或事物
building on top like spring clouds that
像春天的云一样在顶部建造
need to provide some some common
需要提供一些共同点
configuration to these things so maybe
配置这些东西，所以也许
they want to register some interceptors
他们想注册一些拦截器
with every rest template that's being
与每个其余的模板
created for for metrics as I just showed
为我刚刚显示的指标而创建
you or distributed tracing with sleuth
您或使用侦探进行分布式跟踪
or service discovery so we can do some
或服务发现，以便我们可以做一些
additional stuff
其他东西
there's also supporting this for testing
也支持测试
for example on setting up mock MVC so so
例如关于设置模拟MVC
how do you actually make sure that all
您如何真正确保所有
of the instances that are created in
在以下实例中创建的实例
your application get this shared
您的应用程序得到共享
configuration and a common pattern for
配置和通用模式
this in boots is to have builders and
这在靴子是要有建设者和
these builders will be created by boots
这些建造者将由靴子创造
some other configuration there will be a
其他一些配置将有一个
single instance but you can customize
单实例，但您可以自定义
these things by creating your own beans
通过创建自己的bean这些东西
of some customizer type actually I saw
我看到的一些定制器类型
in the presentation on migrating to the
在有关迁移到
latest bring cloud stuff today that
今天带来的最新云内容
they're actually going to have just a
他们实际上将只有一个
generic customizer interface which will
通用的定制器接口
just be parametrized for this but there
只是为此而参数化，但是
are a lot of concretes interfaces there
那里有很多具体的接口
as well and the idea is that these
以及想法是，这些
builders will automatically find all of
建筑商将自动找到所有
these customizers and these customizers
这些定制器和这些定制器
will either customize the builder or the
将自定义构建器或
result of what the builder creates like
建筑商创造的结果
a rest template and then everywhere in
休息模板，然后到处
your application where you need a rest
您需要休息的应用程序
and letour you need an object mapper
让我们需要一个对象映射器
you will just use the corresponding
您将只使用相应的
builder you inject it into your code and
生成器，您将其注入代码并
you say give me the corresponding
你说给我相应的
instance maybe after doing some
实例也许​​在做一些之后
additional configuration so another
额外的配置，所以另一个
reason that's boot provides you with
引导的原因为您提供了
these things is that it provides some
这些事情是因为它提供了一些
norm default configuration or default
规范默认配置或默认
configuration
组态
that's different from the defaults
这与默认值不同
provided by the native libraries so you
由本机库提供，因此您
can have some boot specific opinionated
可以有一些引导特定的意见
defaults for example with Jackson we
例如杰克逊的默认值
will just get an object member that
只会得到一个对象成员
doesn't that simply ignores unknown
那不是简单地忽略未知
fields with a rest Amplatz you will get
休息的Amplatz您将得到
an HTTP client configured based on
基于以下内容配置的HTTP客户端
whatever is on your class path that sort
课堂上的任何东西
of stuff
的东西
and this is all done in for the rest
其余的都做完了
template in all the configuration so I
所有配置中的模板，所以我
want to show you something here where
想给你看一些东西
it's I want to show the importance of
我想表明它的重要性
using the builders so we have another
使用建造者，所以我们还有另一个
application here close own and stop this
此处的应用程序自己关闭并停止
there we go so we have a very simple
我们去那里，所以我们有一个非常简单的
spring boot application as you can see
如您所见，Spring Boot应用程序
it just starts up and then what it does
它只是启动，然后做什么
is it configures this self invoking
它配置了这种自我调用
controller which is a rest controller
控制器是休息控制器
with a first and a second path mapping
具有第一和第二路径映射
and then in the first it will use a rest
然后在第一个它将使用休息
template to make a call to the second
调用第二个模板
that's all it does and currently we have
仅此而已，目前我们拥有
this field rest template where we're
我们在此字段休息模板
just creating the rest template
只是创建其余模板
ourselves also and I'm not going to show
也是我们自己，我不会展示
you because I want to save some time I
你，因为我想节省一些时间
have configured a dependency on Sleuth
已配置对Sleuth的依赖
so that means I'm gonna get distributed
所以这意味着我要去分发
tracing support in this application and
跟踪此应用程序中的支持，以及
then I'm now going to start out the
那我现在就开始
application and then when it started up
应用程序，然后在启动时
I'm going to make a request to slash
我要下斜线
first which will use the configured rest
首先，它将使用配置的其余部分
template to make a call to seconds and
模板以调用秒和
then returns the results right so 8080
然后正确返回结果，所以8080
slash first it gives me a hello from
斜杠首先给我打招呼
seconds exactly as expected and now I
完全符合预期，现在我
have some logging here now this logging
现在在这里记录一些日志
is actually showing some numbers and
实际上显示一些数字，
this is distributed tracing from sleuth
这是从侦探进行的分布式跟踪
and the first numbers here which I want
还有我想要的第一个数字
to point out these are trace IDs the
指出这些是跟踪ID
idea is that when a request comes in we
想法是，当有请求进入时，我们
can create a unique number and we can
可以创建一个唯一的号码，我们可以
propagate that to downstream calls so
将其传播给下游调用
that we can get the same number in all
我们可以得到相同的数字
of our logging which is really nice if
我们的日志记录，如果
you're doing micro services based
您正在基于微服务
architectures but you see here that we
建筑，但您在这里看到我们
don't actually get the same numbers when
实际上，当
we get back when we get back into the
当我们回到
controller
控制者
and do the call to slash second we
并呼吁第二次削减
actually get a different trace ID and
实际上获得了不同的跟踪ID，并且
that is because our rest template has
那是因为我们的休息模板有
not been configured appropriately also
也没有适当配置
going back to my browser trying to
回到我的浏览器试图
actually get the metrics they're not
实际获得的指标不是
there they're there are no metrics
他们那里没有指标
currently configured for the rest of
目前已配置为
even though I did make a request and the
即使我确实提出了要求，
problem is I was creating this rest
问题是我正在创建此休息
template here myself rather than through
我自己而不是通过模板
a builder so what I'm gonna do is I'm
一个建筑商，所以我要做的是
gonna get rid of this trying to make
要摆脱这种试图使
sure to inject the actual rest template
确保注入实际的休息模板
here and I'm getting an error already
在这里，我已经收到一个错误
because I haven't configured any rest
因为我没有休息
template beam so I'm gonna do that next
模板光束，所以我下一步要做
and say I need a beam of type rest
说我需要休息一下
templates inject the rest template
模板注入其余模板
builder here and then say return in my
建造者在这里，然后说回我
case just builder to build I don't need
案例建造者，我不需要
any additional configuration and now
任何其他配置，现在
when I restart my application what will
当我重新启动应用程序时
happen is I will get a rest template
碰巧我会得到一个休息模板
configured through the Builder and there
通过构建器进行配置
will be some additional building
将是一些额外的建筑
configuration from the various framework
来自各种框架的配置
I have on my class path applied to the
我在上课时已将
rest template for me
我的休息模板
so that means when I go back here and I
所以这意味着当我回到这里
make another request is less first and
再次提出另一个要求
it says hello from second and this time
从第二次开始打个招呼
you can see I'm actually getting three
你可以看到我实际上得到了三个
of the same trace at a year rather than
一年的痕迹相同，而不是
just a single one that's different for
只是一个不同的
the second call and refreshing this I
第二个电话，刷新我
now get my metrics back again as well
现在也可以重新获取我的指标
right so that's one of the reasons that
对，这就是原因之一
you should be using these builders now
您应该现在使用这些构建器
I'm not gonna demo it but it turns out
我不会演示，但事实证明
that actually if I would have created a
实际上，如果我会创建一个
beam but I wouldn't have used a builder
梁，但我不会使用建筑商
I would just have set richer a new
我本来可以定一个新的
arrest template I would actually still
逮捕模板我实际上仍然会
get to distribute the tracing support
分发跟踪支持
but I wouldn't get the metric support so
但我无法获得指标支持
it would sort of work you may wonder why
可能会有些奇怪，为什么
that is and actually it's because sleuth
那实际上是因为侦探
does a slightly different trick they use
他们使用的技巧略有不同
some a beam post processor where they
一些光束后处理器
will just take any rest template that
只会采用任何其余的模板
has been configured in the application
已在应用程序中配置
and then they say oh yeah I'm gonna just
然后他们说哦，是的，我要
inject my custom Interceptor as the
将我的自定义拦截器作为
first one to be used in the rest
剩下的要用第一个
template without necessarily doing that
模板，而不必这样做
through a builder but that's not true
通过建设者，但事实并非如此
for all of the support in spring boots
对于春季靴子的所有支撑
so for example like I show the metric
例如，例如，我显示指标
support
支持
it doesn't actually work like that so
它实际上不是那样工作的
you wouldn't still get any metrics for
您仍然不会获得任何指标
this so the advice in general is just
因此，一般的建议只是
always use a builder you'll be good and
总是使用一个建造者，你会很好并且
you can also do your own custom
您也可以自定义
configuration so here for example just
配置，例如这里
to get an idea of what that's like I
了解一下我的情况
have configured a customizer for Jackson
已为Jackson配置了定制程序
which is a sample out of our actual
这是我们实际的样本
application where we say if you want to
我们在这里说您是否想要的应用程序
serialize off set day times which is a
序列化设置的一天时间，这是一个
standard Java its type we want to have
我们想要的标准Java
some different representation of that
对此的一些不同表示
and this will actually ensure that every
这实际上将确保
object mapper in our application that we
在我们的应用程序中的对象映射器
create through spring will have that
通过春天创造将有
configuration appoint there is actually
配置指定实际上
another example but I'm going to skip it
另一个例子，但我要跳过它
now but you will find it in my in my
现在，但是你会在我的
repo where I'm also showing how you
回购，我也在向你展示
could register a custom interceptor to
可以注册一个自定义拦截器
do requests and response logging for
做请求和响应记录
every request that you make with your
您对自己提出的每个请求
rest templates so if you're interested
休息模板，以便您感兴趣
in that make sure to have a look what
在那一定要看看
I'm just going to skip it from now
我现在要跳过它
because there's some other stuff I want
因为我还想要其他东西
to talk about another common thing I
说说我的另一件事
find in building spring applications is
在建筑弹簧应用中发现的是
that you need some customizations for
您需要一些自定义
their local development setup you want
您想要的本地开发设置
to have some different configuration
有一些不同的配置
properties you want to have some spring
你想要一些春天的属性
beans in a different setup because you
豆使用其他设置，因为您
don't want to have security enabled or
不想启用安全性或
you need some different URLs configured
您需要配置一些不同的URL
or you don't integrate with something
否则你不会与某些东西融合
like server discovery and that sort of
例如服务器发现之类的
thing or shared configuration services
事物或共享配置服务
so so how do you set that up and a
因此，您如何设置它并
common solution for this is where people
常见的解决方案是人们
will just use a spring profile it says
只会使用说的弹簧轮廓
I'm gonna define a local print spring
我要定义一个本地印刷弹簧
profile and then I get automatic support
个人资料，然后我会自动获得支持
from boots for some customized
从靴子一些定制
configuration properties like
配置属性，例如
application - local the properties and
应用程序-本地属性和
next to that I can have my custom
接下来，我可以进行自定义
configuration beans in place so I can
配置Bean到位，这样我就可以
have spring configuration that's just
具有弹簧配置
tailored to my local local development
量身定制适合我当地的发展
environment so that's something that you
环境，这就是你
may already be using today the thing is
今天可能已经在使用
if you want to enable a spring profile
如果要启用弹簧轮廓
the typical way to do that is to use
典型的方法是使用
spring doc profile so the active
春天的文档配置文件，所以活跃
property now I'm working on the
现在我正在研究财产
microservices based architecture with
基于微服务的架构
like 30 services or something like that
例如30项服务或类似的服务
I really don't want to have to specify
我真的不想指定
that property in every run configuration
每个运行配置中的该属性
in my IDE for example for all 30
在我的IDE中，例如所有30个
services so how do you deal with that
服务，那么您如何处理
now one way for that could be to say I'm
现在一种方式可能是说我
gonna make all of my developers
会让我所有的开发人员
configure a environment variable which
配置一个环境变量
is called spring profiles active and
被称为弹簧轮廓激活和
that will actually automatically bind
实际上会自动绑定
through the spring profiles at active
通过活动的弹簧轮廓
because of relaxed binding support and
由于宽松的绑定支持和
then you will have that local profile
那么您将拥有该本地资料
whenever your run locally and not
每当您在本地运行时
whenever you run somewhere else that's
每当你跑到其他地方
actually a nice solution however there
实际上是一个不错的解决方案
is a problem there if you want to
如果你想在那里是一个问题
configure some additional profiles then
然后配置一些其他配置文件
you will be likely to just overwrite the
您可能会覆盖
spring profiles active that was
弹簧轮廓激活
configured through the environments
通过环境配置
because these things are do not add to
因为这些东西不会增加
the same property that just overwrite so
只是覆盖了相同的属性
for this something that most people have
为此，大多数人都拥有
noted are not familiar with is that
注意到不熟悉的是
there is a spring the profiles are
有一个弹簧轮廓
include property so rather than saying
包括财产而不是说
spring pro was active you can configure
spring pro处于活动状态，您可以配置
a spring profiles includes which will
弹簧轮廓包括
actually add to any of the profiles that
实际上添加到任何配置文件中
you have activated through the profiles
您已通过配置文件激活
of active thing so what we do in our
积极的事情，所以我们在我们做什么
project and I can show you is that I
项目，我可以告诉你的是，我
have some environment variable here
这里有一些环境变量
which is called spring profiles include
所谓的弹簧轮廓包括
which I've set to local which means that
我将其设置为本地，这意味着
whenever I start up a spring boot app on
每当我启动Spring Boot应用程序时
my local machine I will have a local
我的本地机器，我将有一个本地
profile active in addition to anything
个人资料有效
else that may or may not have been good
否则可能好不好
fear the other thing here by the way
顺便担心这里的另一件事
ensures that I always get nice colored
确保我总是得到漂亮的色彩
output from spring boots in my console
控制台中的弹簧靴的输出
because even though I'm running on
因为即使我在继续
Windows I think I still deserve to have
Windows，我认为我仍然值得拥有
some color as a developer when I'm
当我成为开发人员时有些色彩
running on the command line and this is
在命令行上运行，这是
not enabled by default so what can you
默认情况下未启用，那么您能做什么
configure for local developments well
做好当地发展的配置
it's typically stuff like unique boards
它通常像独特的板子一样
per service right we're running on
我们运行的每个服务权利
docker so in production everything is
码头工人，所以在生产中一切都是
port 8080 and it binds to some random
端口8080，并绑定到一些随机
port at runtime but we're not running
在运行时移植，但我们没有运行
everything in local in docker run we're
docker本地运行的所有内容
running locally we just started boot up
在本地运行，我们刚刚开始启动
so they need a unique server port number
所以他们需要一个唯一的服务器端口号
there's disabling functionality you
有禁用的功能
don't actually want to have for enabling
实际上并不需要启用
things you just want to have when you're
你只是想拥有的东西
running locally so this is just some
在本地运行，所以这只是一些
examples of that one particular example
一个特定例子的例子
I wanted to mention here is logging even
我想说的是这里甚至在记录日志
if you have dedicated log back file you
如果您有专用的日志文件
can still do some customizations through
仍然可以通过以下方式进行一些自定义
spring boot properties so you could say
春天的引导属性，所以你可以说
for example well we slew that has showed
例如，好吧，我们已经证明了
you you get all of this output where
您将获得所有这些输出，其中
there's a trace ID and there's a span ID
有一个跟踪ID和一个跨度ID
and they say if the span will be
他们说跨度是否会
exported or not it's just not useful
是否导出它只是没有用
typically locally I just interested
通常我只是在本地感兴趣
the tres ideal and by saying oh I'm just
特雷斯（tres）理想之选
going to override the the logging
将覆盖日志记录
veteran level here with this custom
这个习惯的老将级
setting I can make sure that I only see
设置我可以确保只看到
the trace at a locally and not half of
痕迹在本地而不是一半
my screen is actually used by the others
我的屏幕实际上已被其他人使用
configuration there or I can do custom
在那里配置或我可以自定义
log level customization for local
本地日志级别的自定义
development so that's some of the things
发展，这就是其中的一部分
that are useful there that's see yeah we
那里有用的，是的，我们
still have five minutes so next thing I
还有五分钟，所以我接下来
want to show you is something that I
想表明你是我的东西
encountered when migrating existing
迁移现有时遇到
applications onto spring boots so what
弹簧靴上的应用程序
I've done a lot myself as well is that
我自己也做了很多事情
when you're running a an applet spring
当您运行小程序春天时
application without boots and you need
没有靴子的应用程序，您需要
to read some configuration resources
阅读一些配置资源
things like key stores for example and
例如密钥库之类的东西，
other files from somewhere you're just
您所在位置的其他文件
going to configure an external class
将配置一个外部类
spot directory the nice thing about
现货目录的好处
doing it like that is that people will
这样做是因为人们会
be able to update these files and change
能够更新这些文件并进行更改
them without creating a new deployments
他们而不创建新的部署
because they're just external to the app
因为它们只是在应用程序外部
but your app still doesn't need to know
但您的应用仍然不需要知道
where these files are located because
这些文件所在的位置，因为
you can configure the class path outside
您可以在外部配置类路径
of the application itself so I used to
应用程序本身，所以我曾经
use that mechanism actually quite a lot
实际上使用了很多机制
but then spring boot came along with its
但是后来弹簧靴随之而来
default packaging mechanism of saying
预设包装机制的说法
we're going to put everything in a fat
我们将把所有东西都放进去
you are this is a fat jar and and that's
你是一个胖胖的罐子，那是
your class buff right you're going to
你的班级爱好者，你要
get your boot in flip and your booting
启动您的靴子并启动
classes from inside the jar and that's
罐子里的类，那是
it and if you don't want to migrate an
它，如果您不想迁移
application to that but your customized
应用程序，但您定制
are ready to reading a lot of stuff from
准备从中阅读很多东西
external class path directories that's
外部类路径目录
going to be a problem now the good news
现在将成为一个问题
is that there is a built-in solution for
是有一个内置的解决方案
this but again it's my experience that a
这不过是我的经验
lot of people don't know about this
很多人对此一无所知
because a Buddha app is started up using
因为Buddha应用程序是使用
a launcher but you can tell it to use a
启动器，但您可以告诉它使用
different launcher than the default one
与默认启动器不同的启动器
now you do this through configuring
现在，您可以通过配置
so-called layouts in your plugin so if
插件中的所谓布局，如果
you're making it looks like this
你让它看起来像这样
actually if you configure this the
实际上，如果您配置此
actual layout the way that your fat jar
实际布局，您的胖子罐子
is created is not really all that
被创造的并不是全部
difference but it will use a different
差异，但会使用不同的
main class as your launcher and oops
主类作为发射器和哎呀
sorry that was one too quick and that
抱歉，那太快了，那个
launcher is called a properties launcher
启动器称为属性启动器
if you use a zip layout now with the
如果您现在将zip布局与
properties launcher what you can do is
属性启动器，您可以做的是
you can configure one or more external
您可以配置一个或多个外部
directories to be added to your class
要添加到您的班级的目录
but that's startup the way that this
但这就是这种方式的启动
works is it look
看起来好吗
for a file called loader the properties
对于名为loader的文件的属性
in the root of your clan spawn so you
在氏族产卵的根部
could package it up with your
可以和你的一起打包
application or you can figure this
应用程序，或者你可以解决这个问题
through the manifest or even through
通过清单甚至
environment variables if you want to
环境变量，如果您想
make this more dynamic and then you can
使它更具动态性，然后您就可以
configure in either of those locations a
在这两个位置中的任何一个进行配置
property called loader dot path with one
一个称为加载程序点路径的属性
or more comma separated directories
或多个逗号分隔的目录
these will be added automatically to
这些将自动添加到
your class but when your application
你的课，但是当你的申请
starts up so I have a little demo for
启动，所以我有一个小演示
that as well let's see here
那也让我们看看这里
so in this case what I have is I have a
所以在这种情况下，我有一个
very simple app all it does that startup
非常简单的应用程序，它可以完成启动
is it reads a file called thrust or AES
它读取的文件名为推力或AES
from the class path to route of the
从课程路径到
class path and then prints out the
类路径，然后打印出
actual configured aliases of the
实际配置的别名
certificates in that in that key store
该密钥库中的证书
or trust or and I have a loader that
或信任，或者我有一个加载程序
properties file here which is configured
此处配置的属性文件
to read a directory called access for
读取一个名为access的目录
exome extensions and I actually have an
外显子组扩展，我实际上有一个
X directory here with a trust or jes and
带有信任或jes的X目录，以及
a lock back dot XML so now what I'm
锁定点XML，现在我是
going to do is I'm actually going to
我要做的是
drop down on a command line I'm gonna do
在命令行上放下
a build of this application and the
此应用程序的构建以及
reason I'm going on to the command line
我继续使用命令行的原因
here is I actually want to have this jar
这实际上是我想要这个罐子
I don't want to run this thing from addy
我不想从阿迪那里跑这东西
I want to simulate this setup where I'm
我想在这里模拟此设置
actually running a fat jar in production
实际上在生产中运行一个胖子罐
but next to that jar as you can see here
但是在那个罐子旁边，你可以在这里看到
I have my X directory right and that's
我的X目录正确，那是
where I'm gonna read the load logback
我要在其中读取加载日志的地方
dot xml from and I'm gonna read this
点xml来自，我要读这篇
actual trustor file from my command-line
我的命令行中的实际信任者文件
runner so what I can do now is I can say
跑步者，所以我现在可以说
Java
爪哇
- card targets external snapshot the jar
-卡针对罐子的外部快照
so it's will start up and you can notice
所以它会启动，你会注意到
two things here first of all I have some
首先，我有两件事
actual logging here and second of all
实际记录在这里，第二
there is the output here that says I've
这里有说我已经
loaded the trustor and I found three
加载了委托人，我发现了三个
different certificates in this thing I
我在这东西上有不同的证书
can show you that this works because if
可以告诉你这可行，因为如果
I would move to the
我会搬到
directory now and I would try to start
目录现在，我会尝试开始
the same thing from here it won't work
从这里开始同样的事情是行不通的
because that X directory was actually
因为那个X目录实际上是
relative to my working directory so
相对于我的工作目录
right now it's actually failing with the
现在实际上是失败了
final found because as I I don't have
最终发现是因为II没有
this file I cannot read this trust or at
我无法读取此文件或在
startup so one of the results of doing
启动，所以做的结果之一
this is that someone could now actually
这是有人现在可以
change your law configuration outside of
在外部更改法律配置
your application but still the look-back
您的应用程序，但回头看
dot XML is just read from the class path
点XML只是从类路径中读取
as is common for for most applications
对于大多数应用程序来说很常见
right I'm using another feature here
对，我在这里使用另一个功能
where we're actually importing some
我们实际上正在导入一些
default boot configuration and we'll
默认启动配置，我们将
walk back so I don't have to setup
向后走，所以我不必设置
everything myself so that's pretty much
我自己的一切，所以差不多
done so in conclusion because time is up
结论是这样做的，因为时间到了
I think food is awesome but that doesn't
我认为食物很棒，但是那不
mean that you should just be satisfied
意味着你应该感到满意
with ever it brings out of the box right
与它带来了开箱即用的权利
it's a framework that very easily allows
这个框架很容易允许
you to configure stuff or to actually
您配置的东西或实际
use the same mechanisms that boot uses
使用引导使用的相同机制
internally for your own application so
内部为您自己的应用程序，所以
you should look into those customization
你应该研究那些定制
and configuration options there it
和那里的配置选项
really pays off to read configuration or
真正有回报的阅读配置或
what's actually much better is to have
实际上更好的是
someone like me doing that for you
像我这样的人为你做
diving into this figuring it all out and
潜入这个弄清楚一切，
then explaining it in a 50 minute talk
然后在50分钟的演讲中进行解释
on a conference so thank you very much
在会议上，非常感谢
for attending if you want to look at
如果你想看参加
this code yourself play around with it
这个代码你自己玩
oh my get up I've pushed this it's under
哦，我起床了，我把它推到了
a boot loop project I've also uploaded
我还上传了一个引导循环项目
the slides are ready to SlideShare and
幻灯片已准备好与SlideShare和
once the the video is up I will actually
视频播放完后，我实际上
add the YouTube video to that slide deck
将YouTube视频添加到该幻灯片
so you can follow along obligatory we're
这样您就可以按照我们的要求
hiring slides we have electrical cars
租用幻灯片，我们有电动汽车
and boats so it's super cool thanks
和船，这真是太酷了，谢谢
everyone for attending time is up but if
每个人的参加时间都到了，但是如果
you have any questions I will be I will
你有任何问题我会的
be around here so a please come up to me
在这里，所以请来找我
and we can talk some more thank you very
我们可以再谈一点谢谢
much
许多
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]